<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://jameswathomson.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://jameswathomson.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-05-02T10:32:16+00:00</updated><id>https://jameswathomson.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">If it’s not broken…</title><link href="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/old-vs-new-speakers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="If it’s not broken…"/><published>2025-04-30T16:40:16+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-30T16:40:16+00:00</updated><id>https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/old-vs-new-speakers</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/old-vs-new-speakers/"><![CDATA[<p>Recently my daughter developed a keen urge to buy a turntable and some vinyl, and then asked me how much I may have stored away. This ended up with me bringing 5 boxes down from the loft, and at some point my own turntable when I find it. I now also have been given some excellent 1970s speakers which I will hopefully attach to a 1970’s amplifier and 1970’s cassette deck, and 1990’s turntable.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="https://www.diyaudio.com/forums/attachments/multi-way/323189d1357929498-celestion-ditton-44-sounding-muddy-celestion_ditton_44-loudspeakers-speaker-002-jpg" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="https://www.diyaudio.com/forums/attachments/multi-way/323189d1357929498-celestion-ditton-44-sounding-muddy-celestion_ditton_44-loudspeakers-speaker-002-jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/50/Technics_SL-1200MK2-2/1200px-Technics_SL-1200MK2-2-480.webp 480w,https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/50/Technics_SL-1200MK2-2/1200px-Technics_SL-1200MK2-2-800.webp 800w,https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/50/Technics_SL-1200MK2-2/1200px-Technics_SL-1200MK2-2-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/50/Technics_SL-1200MK2-2.jpg/1200px-Technics_SL-1200MK2-2.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="https://i.redd.it/h04oiddwrdy61-480.webp 480w,https://i.redd.it/h04oiddwrdy61-800.webp 800w,https://i.redd.it/h04oiddwrdy61-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="https://i.redd.it/h04oiddwrdy61.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/nnkAAOSwX~Fm0LbB/s-l1200-480.webp 480w,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/nnkAAOSwX~Fm0LbB/s-l1200-800.webp 800w,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/nnkAAOSwX~Fm0LbB/s-l1200-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/nnkAAOSwX~Fm0LbB/s-l1200.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Celestion Ditton 44 speakers grilles removed [England, 1972], Technics SL1200 Turntable [Japan, 1979], Pioneer SX-750 [Japan, 1977] and Technics 615 Cassette Deck [Japan, 1977] </div> <p>Why the 1970's when there is 50 years of improvements to enjoy? Well, the speakers were free but would be a couple of grand in new money, and a recommended equivalent is at least £3k but may not sound as good according to reviews. I'm not an audiophile by any means but I do like to listen to music, I do this all the time and it keeps me almost sane. I therefore can justify a decent set up but not the modern cost of one.</p> <p>The turntable came from a friend in the 1980's who used to work at Laskys, a popular electrical store. The amp and tape deck were from ebay at a steal some years ago, much more expensive now</p> <p>Do we constantly need to 'upgrade' to the law of diminishing returns? Embrace the past and dig the old kit out of the loft. I never tire of the soft crackle and rumble of vinyl that has been played over and over, music was never meant to sound so clinical.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="technology"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[1970s Technology, does it hold up?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">my initial (proper) experience with GitPages</title><link href="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/gitpages/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="my initial (proper) experience with GitPages"/><published>2025-04-30T14:24:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-30T14:24:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/gitpages</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/gitpages/"><![CDATA[<p>I'd used GitPages previously but never with any proper structure. I decided to move my site here as I had been convinced by this Spencer Pao video from 2022 that using a Jekyll template I could create a blog-like site</p> <iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/g6AJ9qPPoyc" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="web-dev"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[To start the posts]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">#guts2025 | James Thomson</title><link href="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/guts2025-james-thomson/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="#guts2025 | James Thomson"/><published>2025-03-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/guts2025--james-thomson</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/guts2025-james-thomson/"><![CDATA[<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>          Agree &amp; Join LinkedIn
        
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

            Innovative Engineering &amp; Digital Technologies Leader | Driving Excellence in Education &amp; Industry
        What the future of Engineering could hold, from #GUTS2025
    To view or add a comment, sign in

        720 followers
      
              Create your free account or sign in to continue your search
            
          or
        
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

            New to LinkedIn? Join now
          
                    or
                  
              New to LinkedIn? Join now
            
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.
</code></pre></div></div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What the future of Engineering could hold, from #GUTS2025]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Embracing AI: Redefining Education for a Collaborative Future</title><link href="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/embracing-ai-redefining-education-for-a-collaborative-future/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Embracing AI: Redefining Education for a Collaborative Future"/><published>2025-03-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/embracing-ai-redefining-education-for-a-collaborative-future</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/embracing-ai-redefining-education-for-a-collaborative-future/"><![CDATA[<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>          Agree &amp; Join LinkedIn
        
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

              Create your free account or sign in to continue your search
            
          or
        
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

            New to LinkedIn? Join now
          
                    or
                  
              New to LinkedIn? Join now
            
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

      Some years ago I took a short online course called 'The Mind is Flat' which proposes that much of our behavior, thoughts, and feelings are shaped by external influences and immediate contexts, we basically learn from the available surroundings. 
    
      Back in the early 80's when I was first at college our learning was shaped by our tutors and the books available to us despite the fact that at the time I was on a computing course with no internet and even no word processing. The computers were just for programming and everything else was painstakingly handwritten.
    
      In the 1990s the internet appeared and despite the initial novelty and a lack of real depth of information this has grown exponentially over the years, and so has trust in the ability to quickly find resources using this medium. This has not always been the case, a fellow colleague comically shouted to me some years ago in response to learner actions in a computer room 'They're watching YouTube! Can't we stop it?'.
    
      We now have data synthesis in the form of generative AI, or ChatGPT as learners like to call it, which reminds me of people calling the vacuum by the common brand name 'hoover'. This is the scary stuff of many a Sci-Fi horror movie as it makes sense of not just what you are asking but it can seemingly work things out and tell you the answer in a friendly non-robotic way including via voice. I can imagine this horror has been played out several times over with the introduction of calculators, video tapes etc. Technology never stands still.
    
      So for Gen Z, the digital natives there is an expectation that technology will take some of the load of the learning process, even using copy/paste with generative AI. Some people suggest that this dangerous practice is enough for the magical latest technology to be banned. Did they ban the calculator (erm, yes actually in some exams!), were books initially banned (yes, throughout history). 
    
      The point I am making is that technology moves on and education must embrace and evolve with it. You wouldn't paint the Forth Bridge using a toothbrush, so why restrict the opportunities for research that can involve active discussion and collaboration. Rather than being a passive tool, it acts as an engaged participant, helping to refine ideas, explore diverse perspectives, and spark meaningful dialogues. There has always been various shortcuts to 'achievement' and generative AI only serves to show up the education system rather than the other way around. Rather than endless rote learning we are now in the fascinating world of expert analysis and discussion which should be championed. Exams and assignments are no longer fit for purpose, creative thinking should instead replace these with practical projects where problems have to be solved, something which will encourage collaboration with these tools and could lay out thought processes from start to finish. Embracing new ways of measuring achievement would not only stop the copy and paste culture but would encourage growth mindset learning. 
    
      AI may be the stuff of scary sci-fi horror movies but a future filled with repetition-based learning is more robot-like than the natural language processed tools of the future, embrace it!
    Digital Apprenticeship TutorGreat article James Thomson. I'm using AI multiple times a  week to show apprentices how to use it for research and personal learning. My current favorite is https://www.perplexity.ai/ it can review 10's of websites in seconds, always gives multiple further reference areas at the end of it's response and creates a link to the summary it has created that I can share with the apprentice and they can refer back to. Gone are the days of spending all day in the library trolling through a stack of books to find and cross reference learning. Its a fantastic tool in the toolbox to help learning and development.
    To view or add a comment, sign in

              
    I have had a fair few jobs in my time, in industry and also in education over the last 20 years. People come to FE for…
  
            Stay updated on your professional world
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

    New to LinkedIn? Join now
</code></pre></div></div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some years ago I took a short online course called 'The Mind is Flat' which proposes that much of our behavior, thoughts, and feelings are shaped by external influences and immediate contexts, we basically learn from the available surroundings. Back in the early 80's when I was first at college our]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nurturing the Nurturers: Health and Well-being in Further Education</title><link href="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/nurturing-the-nurturers-health-and-well-being-in-further-education/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nurturing the Nurturers: Health and Well-being in Further Education"/><published>2025-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/nurturing-the-nurturers-health-and-well-being-in-further-education</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2025/nurturing-the-nurturers-health-and-well-being-in-further-education/"><![CDATA[<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>          Agree &amp; Join LinkedIn
        
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

              Create your free account or sign in to continue your search
            
          or
        
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

            New to LinkedIn? Join now
          
                    or
                  
              New to LinkedIn? Join now
            
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

      I have had a fair few jobs in my time, in industry and also in education over the last 20 years. People come to FE for a number of reasons. The lure of a fairly secure job with good holidays and a decent pension sometimes attracts the younger crowd, fresh from the other side of the education experience. The other people that are drawn to teaching are people who have experienced life in industry, and maybe see education as an opportunity to give something back, nurturing young aspiring learners into those same careers that served them well. Either way a team is formed and the process of getting a cohort through a year of education is started.
    
      I know people that look upon our profession as something that attracts a lesser-capable person. One who likes short working and long holidays but the reality of FE is very different to that vision. I put teaching in with being a doctor or a policeman in the sense that it must be incredibly difficult to switch off. Mostly my time in industry was confined to the standard working week, once I had clocked off I gave work very little thought. We join the teaching profession because we want to give, and we give it all. Weeks are crammed with interaction in class, with some time for admin such as class preparation, marking and CPD. These often spill over into evenings and weekends and work-life balance contains less life and more work. The saying is if you love your job you'll never work a day in your life. We love our jobs and that is what makes it so attractive but also so overwhelming.
    
      As a manager I have the yearly responsibility of getting hundreds of young people through a qualification but also to engcourage personal growth, the ability to be curious and have a growth mindset. I want all learners to embrace a culture of lifelong learning because education is the foundation of living. An educated population is more likely to contribute positively to society and so we have a great responsibility. I also have line management of around a dozen staff from technicians to trainers to lecturers. Each one of these staff are people with hopes and fears, families and financial responsibilities. I see them more in the week than I do my own family and our shared big responsibility has a huge impact on each and every one of them. Some have been with me for a number of years, some come and go struggling to come to terms with the demands of the job. Often a toll is taken on the physical and mental well-being of consistently high workload. I'm not selling the job but it is incredibly fulfilling!
    
      So what can we do as managers to retain staff and help them through the tough times? I return to the phrase often used, nobody comes to work to do a bad job. In a high stress environment it's easy to get frustrated and look for someone to 'blame' when things don't go as planned. How many times have you heard that a company has no 'blame culture' yet finger points at the first opportunity? I always believe hard work and successful outcomes are a good antidote to those attitudes, but to keep the focus of so many people all the time is a tough job. When the heat is on people tend to get less cooperative when what we always need is more cooperation, and shared responsibility. I have always tried to communicate my way through difficulties. If a member of my team is struggling a solution can be found much easier through an empathetic ear. Remember that people are just like you and I, and that they all strive to be their best selves. Help don't hassle and they will show you that they are all actually amazing individuals. Communication is key but also is time, time to think, time to take a deep breath and go again.
    
      Sounds easy doesn't it and I didn't even mention a pay rise! Look after your staff just as you look after your students (or customers). From the people who keep the offices clean, the people who keep you secure. They all have that word in common, people. They have feelings, please respect that
    Digital Apprenticeship TutorA great read, well done James Thomson.
</code></pre></div></div> <p>We literally change lives, I often think about the apprentices I work with and how their achievements changes their life, from their salary through to opportunities.</p> <p>To create the spark and to see learners turn the spark into a flame and become passionate about what they do is magical.</p> <p>To play to forward and pass it on is amazing and I see that were in great hands with the next generation.Helping to create a strong and appropriate future for employers and their apprentices in engineering and manufacturing.Educators in the FE sector have never recieved the support and acknowledgement they deserve, hence the sector is struggling to recruit and retain staff.Engineering Curriculum Manager (Chesterfield College &amp; Learning Unlimited Derby)This is an excellent read James 🙌🏻 To view or add a comment, sign in</p> <div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>    Some years ago I took a short online course called 'The Mind is Flat' which proposes that much of our behavior…
  
            Stay updated on your professional world
  By clicking Continue to join or sign in, you agree to LinkedIn’s User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Cookie Policy.

    New to LinkedIn? Join now
</code></pre></div></div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have had a fair few jobs in my time, in industry and also in education over the last 20 years. People come to FE for a number of reasons.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with custom blockquotes</title><link href="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2023/custom-blockquotes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with custom blockquotes"/><published>2023-05-12T19:53:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-12T19:53:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2023/custom-blockquotes</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jameswathomson.github.io/blog/2023/custom-blockquotes/"><![CDATA[<p>This post shows how to add custom styles for blockquotes. Based on <a href="https://github.com/sighingnow/jekyll-gitbook">jekyll-gitbook</a> implementation.</p> <p>We decided to support the same custom blockquotes as in <a href="https://sighingnow.github.io/jekyll-gitbook/jekyll/2022-06-30-tips_warnings_dangers.html">jekyll-gitbook</a>, which are also found in a lot of other sites’ styles. The styles definitions can be found on the <a href="https://github.com/alshedivat/al-folio/blob/main/_sass/_base.scss">_base.scss</a> file, more specifically:</p> <div class="language-scss highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="cm">/* Tips, warnings, and dangers */</span>
<span class="nc">.post</span> <span class="nc">.post-content</span> <span class="nt">blockquote</span> <span class="p">{</span>
  <span class="k">&amp;</span><span class="nc">.block-tip</span> <span class="p">{</span>
    <span class="nl">border-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-tip-block</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="nl">background-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-tip-block-bg</span><span class="p">);</span>

    <span class="nt">p</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-tip-block-text</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>

    <span class="nt">h1</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h2</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h3</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h4</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h5</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h6</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-tip-block-title</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>
  <span class="p">}</span>

  <span class="k">&amp;</span><span class="nc">.block-warning</span> <span class="p">{</span>
    <span class="nl">border-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-warning-block</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="nl">background-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-warning-block-bg</span><span class="p">);</span>

    <span class="nt">p</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-warning-block-text</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>

    <span class="nt">h1</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h2</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h3</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h4</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h5</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h6</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-warning-block-title</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>
  <span class="p">}</span>

  <span class="k">&amp;</span><span class="nc">.block-danger</span> <span class="p">{</span>
    <span class="nl">border-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-danger-block</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="nl">background-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-danger-block-bg</span><span class="p">);</span>

    <span class="nt">p</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-danger-block-text</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>

    <span class="nt">h1</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h2</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h3</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h4</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h5</span><span class="o">,</span>
    <span class="nt">h6</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-danger-block-title</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>
  <span class="p">}</span>
<span class="p">}</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>A regular blockquote can be used as following:</p> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="gt">&gt; This is a regular blockquote</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; and it can be used as usual</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <blockquote> <p>This is a regular blockquote and it can be used as usual</p> </blockquote> <p>These custom styles can be used by adding the specific class to the blockquote, as follows:</p> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="gt">&gt; ##### TIP</span>
<span class="gt">&gt;</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; A tip can be used when you want to give advice</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; related to a certain content.</span>
{: .block-tip }
</code></pre></div></div> <blockquote class="block-tip"> <h5 id="tip">TIP</h5> <p>A tip can be used when you want to give advice related to a certain content.</p> </blockquote> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="gt">&gt; ##### WARNING</span>
<span class="gt">&gt;</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; This is a warning, and thus should</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; be used when you want to warn the user</span>
{: .block-warning }
</code></pre></div></div> <blockquote class="block-warning"> <h5 id="warning">WARNING</h5> <p>This is a warning, and thus should be used when you want to warn the user</p> </blockquote> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="gt">&gt; ##### DANGER</span>
<span class="gt">&gt;</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; This is a danger zone, and thus should</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; be used carefully</span>
{: .block-danger }
</code></pre></div></div> <blockquote class="block-danger"> <h5 id="danger">DANGER</h5> <p>This is a danger zone, and thus should be used carefully</p> </blockquote> ]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="blockquotes"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with custom blockquotes]]></summary></entry></feed>